3339 N Kenmore Ave. Unit 2 Chicago, IL 60657 813-335-5655 dsparr1010@gmail.com

Debra Sparr

Objective

Server and bartender with 10 years of experience seeking to transfer interpersonal skills gained in the service industry to obtain a challenging entry-level software position. As a college graduate with degrees in Philosophy and Anthropology, the unique qualitative and quantitative analytical reasoning skills obtained allows for a creative and detailed ability to develop effective and efficient solutions.

Experience

Sep 2016 - Apr 2019 **Penthouse** New Orleans, LA

Cocktail Server

- Consistently shown to be a teamplayer by aiding my fellow coworkers with high levels of problem solving skills, positivity, and empathy.
- Monitored guests at all times, predicted needs and quickly responded to requests through active listening.
- Prioritized procedures with quests by maintaining ability to multitask and be decisive.
- Approached guest complaints and conflict in the workplace with impartiality and patience.

Mar 2016 - Sep 2016 Coyote Ugly New Orleans, LA

Bartender

- Demonstrated the ability to multi-task at a face pace while dealing with various situations/individuals with over 800 customers weekly.
- Created a welcoming environment for visiting guests through a polite and sociable demeanor.
- Created marketing strategies through the use of social media to promote the business and increase sales.

Dec 2015 – Mar 2016 The Swamp New Orleans, LA

Bartender

- Used judgment and people skills to work out any customer issues effectively solving the issue and maintaining or gaining customer loyalty.
- Praised for consistently showing the ability to work under pressure in high volume and fast paced environment with a calm demeanor.
- Through adaptability and hardwork, obtained the highest sales in the history of The Swamp.

Mar 2014 - Sep 2015

Server and Bottle Server

The Lodge

Tampa, FL

- Trained new hires conveying knowledge and skills to employees as well as continually mentoring them throughout their learning process.
- Allocated time management efficiently working 35 40 hours while enrolled as a full time double major student.
- Established a loyal and repeat clientele base by consistently creating a memorable environment for guests, executing procedures in a timely fashion, and ensuring guest satisfaction.
- Self-created and implemented service strategy that focused on both profitability and the customer's need, resulting in a positive outcome for all parties.

Education

University of South Florida

Tampa, FL

- Bachelor of Arts Degree in Anthropology
 - Concentration in linguistic anthropology
 - 3.2 Overall GPA
 - Crystal River Early Village Archaeological Project (CREVAP) archaeological internship
- Bachelor of Arts Degree in Philosophy
 - 3.2 Overall GPA
- Alumna of Sigma Delta Tau Women's Fraternity
 - Nationally recognized "Diamond Chapter"
 - Greek Relations Chair
 - Raised over \$50,000 annually for our philanthropy, Prevent Child Abuse America (PCAA), by holding a popular Greek-wide event called "Putting on the Hits"
 - Annually held "Flower Project" to raise money for Jewish Women's International an
 organization that works to break the cycle of violence against women and girls; ensure
 women's economic independence; and build women's leadership

Additional Skills and Certificates

- Software proficiency Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Google Drive
- Basic knowledge of Java, Javascript, HTML, and CSS
- Basset and Food Handler Certificate

Volunteering Experience

- Garfield Park Conservatory
 - General Horticulture and Composting departments
- New Orleans City Park volunteer
 - Horticulture apprentice